

Mobile:

+92 302 2354195

Email:

Nasirktk065@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/Nasir-

Iqbal5

Github:

https://github.com/ii

AmNasir

Personal Portfolio:

https://nasir-

iqbal.herokuapp.com/

Address:

House 10, Street 3, Azmat Town, Bhara Kahu, Islamabad

Professional Skills

- Python, Flask, Django
- Pytorch, Keras
- Git Version Control
- HTML, CSS, JS
- Oracle, SQL
- React JS, Java

Soft Skills

- AI-Enthusiast & Fast Learner
- Problem solving
- Team Work
- Communication Skills
- Microsoft Tools (Word, Excel)

Hobbies

- Read tech blogs
- Coding
- Hiking
- Play Table Tennis

Interests

- Backend Web Developer [Python/Django or Flask]
- Software Engineer
- Machine Learning
- Full Stack Web Developer [Django/Flask+React JS]

Nasir Iqbal (Software Engineer)

Professional Goals

Motivated Computer Science graduate from National university of computer & emerging Sciences with highly experienced in Python, OOP, Database System and Machine learning. Worked as Teaching Assistant of Advanced Programming for 4 months. Aiming for a job as Software Engineer in your company so that I can serve & learn from your company and make a difference in this field.

Education

FAST-National University Of Computer & Emerging Science(NUCES)

B.S(Computer Science) August 2017 - January 2022

Work Experience

FAST-NUCES Islamabad

Teaching Assistant of Advanced Programing
Sept 01, 2021 - January 15, 2022

Freelancer.com

Python Developer July 01, 2021 - current

Final Year Project

Wise Translator

Python | Flask | JavaScript | Final Year Project | March 2021 - December 2021

- A Web Application Which Translate Text between English and Urdu.
- We build and train deep learning model which gives better accuracy than google translator.

Projects

Al based Controller For Flappy Bird Game

Python | Pygame | Neural Network

- In this Project I have build an intelligent agent using artificial neural network with genetic algorithm. The agent is able to play Flappy bird better than human.

Beautify

Python | Tkinter | OpenCv

- A simple desktop application which can be used for editing pictures.

Smart Parking System

Java | JavaFx | MySql

- A Desktop application which can be used to manage parking system of institution.
- Used Scrum iterative model to complete application within the given time.

Personal Portfolio

HTML | CSS | JavaScript

- I have designed a web based personal portfolio Website using HTML and CSS and Java Script.

SecureChat Application using AES

Java | Android

- This is a cryptography project in which I have developed an android based secure chat application that encode/decode messages using different mode of AES.